Marshall和Lily在一起度过了9年美好时光
Marshall and Lily had been together for nine wonderful years,
直到她甩了他 只身前往旧金山
until she dumped him and ran off to san francisco.
而复原的过程花了很长一段时间
The healing process was taking a long time.
直到有一天晚上 他却向前迈出了很大一步
then, one night, he made a giant leap forward.
好吧, 我想我该走了
All right, I'll see you guys later.
- 我送你出去 - 拜
- I'll walk you out. - See ya.
你刚才盯着Robin的屁股
You just checked out robin's ass.
什么? 哦不不, Barney, 我只是...
What? No!N-no, barney, I was...
伙计, 这真是太棒了
dude, that's awesome.
你终于忘记那个红头发侏儒了
You're finally forgetting about that short redhead.
- 哦是的, Lily, 谢谢你提醒我
- Lily. - Yes, lily.Thank you.
今天晚上我的脑子总是不太好使
That was going to drive me crazy all night.
嘿, Ted, Marshall刚才居然盯着 你女朋友的屁股看
Hey, ted, marshall just checked out your girlfriend's ass.
- 我没有, Ted, 我... - 棒极了
- I did not, ted, I... - that's awesome.
你终于好转了
You're finally getting better.
这一刻我等了好久
This is the moment I've been waiting for.
今晚开始, 我将教你怎么做人
Starting tonight, I am going to teach you how to live.
Ted, 给过你机会了
Ted, you had your chance.
你出局, Marshall上场
You're out; marshall's in.
- 太棒了 - 哦, 别这样
- Yes! - Oh, god.
Marshall, 在纽约做一个光棍就像是...
Marshall, being a single guy in new york city is like...
人们都喜欢什么东西?
what's something everybody likes?
糖果
Candy.
是的, 就像在一家糖果店
Yes, it's like being in a candy store.
进去然后专挑一些特大号的
You just walk right in and grab yourself some whoppers.
好吧
yeah.
特大号的就是最好的?
Is whoppers the best one?
有坚果的才好
Mounds.
牛奶吐司
Milk dudS.
变色豆
Gobstoppers.
这个讨论持续了几个小时 就直接跳到结果吧
This went on for another hour; I'll just skip to the end.
双爆口香糖(双飞)
Dubble bubbles.
不错
Nice!
Marshall, 就是这样
Marshall. We're doing this.
- 我可不想听到你的答案是不 - 好吧
- I am not taking no for an answer. - Fine.
嘿, Robin
hey, robin.
Marshall刚才盯着你的屁股看呢
Marshall checked out your ass.
Ted, 你怎么这样?
Ted, what is wrong with you?
他在看我的屁股
He checked out my ass.
帮我谢谢他 我一直觉得今天我的屁股不怎么好看
Hey, tell him thanks.I felt like I was having a bad ass day.
酷, 回见
Cool, see ya.
Lily
Lily.
屁股很棒
It is a great ass.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
时间轴: YTET-13wolf 翻译:Roddick 校对:魔女佳莉 - =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET-13wolf - =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
老爸老妈罗曼史 第二季第二集
How I Met Your Mother Season 2 Episode 2
我们已经3个月没有见到Lily了
None of us had seen Lily In three months.
有太多的问题需要搞清楚 她们之间太多话要说
There were so many unanswered questions, so many things to say.
你的发型很可爱啊
Your hair is adorable.
与此同时, Barney带着Marshall出去找女人 这是他17岁以后的第一次
meanwhile, barney was taking marshall out to meet women for the first time since he was 17.
嗨, 见过Marshall吗?
Hi.Have you met marshall?
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
看我都出手汗了
Look how sweaty my hands are.
很奇怪, 出汗?
It's weird, right? Uh, sweat?
就像是一种难闻的液体从你的皮肤上渗出来
Like, this smelly water coming out of your skin.
见到你很高兴
It was nice meeting you.
我...我讨厌打扰别人 但是, 嗯, 你喜欢魔术吗?
I- I-I hate to interrupt, but, uh, do you like magic?
嗯, 我想是的
Um, I guess.
哦, 太神奇了!
oh, my god!
还有Marshall他非常棒
anyway, marshall here is awesome.
袋中礼花是他的点子
Salad in a bag? His idea.
小子!
Dude!
你昨天晚上表现很好啊
You were awesome last night.
相当有魅力, 风趣 你完全捕获了那个女人的心
You were charming, you were funny, you were totally working that girl.
可是你却带她回家了
You went home with her.
是的
Yes, I did.
不过她说如果不是我的出现
But she told me that if it wasn't for me,
你就有机会和她来一次
you would have had a shot with her,
所以, 昨晚你完全成功了, 很好!
so, in hypothetical terms, you scored last night. All right!
假定击掌
Hypothetical high five.
很好
Nice.
就这样吧
All right.
今晚, 我们再去一家酒吧...
Tonight, we're going to go to the bar...
Barney, 我不会再和你出去了
barney, no, I am not going out with you ever again.
拜托!
Come on!
我会教你我所有的策略
I'll, I'll teach you all of my strategies.
哦是吗?
Oh, really?
我的最爱, 7号策略 给你的一切蒙上一层神秘的面纱
My favorite, number seven: Create a mystery about yourself.
这样就引起了她们的兴趣 他们不得不一个晚上都围着你转
That way, they become so intrigued, they have to hang out with you all night.
哦, 真的管用?
Oh, come on, does that really work?
也许有, 也许没有
Maybe it does, and maybe it doesn'T.
混蛋, 你勾起了我的兴趣
Damn it, that's intriguing.
好吧, 我参加
Okay, I'm in.
- 我有点事情要告诉你 - 你绝对不会相信发生了什么的
- I have something you've got to hear. - You will not believe what just happened.
你先说
You go first.
我在地铁上找到一个1939年的硬币
I found a 1939 penny on the subway.
想像一下, 这个小东西上蕴含了多少历史...
Just imagine the kind of history this little copper guy...
Lily回来了
lily's back in town.
你居然让我先说?
And you let me go first?
- 你们见过面了吗?
- Have you seen her? - Uh, yeah.
其实我和她今天一起去看了房子
I actually went apartment-hunting with her today.
她现在如何?
How's she doing?
你绝对不会喜欢的
You're not going to like it.
我现在感觉很好
I am doing great.
这是一个完美的夏天
This summer, best thing ever!
旧金山绝对值得一去
San francisco is so happening right now.
她还这么开心?!
She's happy?!
Marshall熬过了人生中最糟糕的一个夏天 她居然还这么开心
Marshall had the worst summer of his life, and she's happy.
是的, 我想她的艺术课似乎很完美
Yeah, and I suppose her art program was all fulfilling or whatever.
哦, 那个艺术课程...
Oh.The art program...
简直太棒了
best thing ever.
哦, 上帝
Oh, my god.
这是你最出色的作品
This is your best work.
在我的教学生涯中 我从来没看到过这么...
In all my years teaching, I've never seen anything so...
废话不说了, 这就说是艺术
needless to say, this is art.
我已经没东西可以教给你了
I can't teach you anything.
但是在SF最棒的一部分...
but the best part of S.F.
哦, 我们管旧金山叫SF...
Oh, that's what we call san francisco...
是那里的人
the people.
在公车上也是
Even just riding around on the bus all summer.
简直就像是人类展览馆
It was like a human tapestry.
嗨, 我叫Mike
Hi, I'm mike.
我是一个反佛教徒冒险旅行作家
I'm a buddhist monk slash adventure-traveler writer.
我叫Paula 我是一个专为孩子们唱歌的朋克乐团歌手
I'm paula. I sing in a punk band for children.
是的
Yeah.
我叫Dan, 我是一个神经外科医生
I'm dan, I'm a neurosurgeon.
你很迷人
You are stunning, by the way.
我很为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
哦, 她真是一个...
Oh, she's such A...
在对Marshall的所作所为之后 她又回来来搞破坏
after what she did to marshall, she should come back here devastated,
她完全应该满怀歉意和悔意的
crawling on all fours over the broken glass of her own shame and regret.
不要倾向谁
You never chose sides.
我尊重她的决定
I respect that.
她简直是不可理喻, 无法让人相信
She's unbelievable. Unbelievable.
无法让人相信?
Unbelievable?
什么无法让人相信
What's unbelievable?
听着, Marshall
Listen, marshall.
Ted在地铁上找到一个铜板,旧的 真是有趣
Ted found a penny on the subway, and it's old, and that's interesting.
好样的
Way to go.
好吧, 首先, 那确实有意思
Okay, first of all, that is interesting.
其次, 我们得告诉他
Second, we have to tell him.
不, 我们不能, 他才刚刚恢复过来 才会和Barney一起出去
No, we don'T.He's just starting to get better, going out with barney.
我是说, 如果他听说Lily又有了新欢 会怎么想
I mean, how do you think he's going to feel when he hears lily's moved on?
- 她又有新欢了? - 有可能
- She's moved on? - It happens.
以前我也是这样的
I've fallen out of love faster than that before,
有时候, 完全没有先兆就...
sometimes, boom, with no warning whatsoever.
当天我们还再热恋 第二天, 他在我面前就像死的一样了
One day we're in love, the next day, he's dead to me.
但是我们现在很好 亲爱的
But we're great. Honey.
现在, 我们来复习一下Barney的 关于不要约会只要做爱的战略
Now, let's review barney's rules for mating without dating.
第二课, 第五节
Lesson two, corollary five.
让一个美女清醒感觉自己没有吸引力 这样她就完全在你的股掌之中了
Make a beautiful woman feel self-conscious and unattractive, and she'll be putty in your hands.
很好
Excellent.
- 你决定你的主菜了吗? - 是的
- Have you chosen your entree? - I have.
一个黑皮肤女人, 8点方向
Sweet brunette, eight o'clock.
9点方向
Nine o'clock.
十点...半 她走向吧台了
Ten... thirty. She's walking to the bar.
- 她? 真的? - 是的
- Her? Really? - Yeah.
哦你是对的
No, you're right.
野心是成功最大的敌人
Ambition is the enemy of success.
好吧, 准备出击
Okay.Hit it.
怎么了, 四眼女郎 你有散光还是什么?
what's the matter, four eyes, you got astigmatism or something?
抱歉, 我只是想缓和一下气氛 我刚刚从一段很长的关系中走出来
I'm sorry, I was trying to playfully disarm you, but I just got out of a long relationship.
我完全不知道我在干什么
I have no idea what I'm doing.
- 我叫Marshall - 你好, Marshall 我叫Amy
- I'm marshall. - Hi, marshall. Amy.
别担心, 我也是过来人
Don't worry. I've been there.
等等
Hold on.
不错, 我想起作用了
Nice recovery. I think it's working.
Amy, 这是我的朋友Barney Barney, 这是Amy
Um, amy.This is my friend, barney.Barney, this is amy.
- 嗨, Barney, 很高兴见到你 - 嗨
- Hi, barney.Nice to meet you. - Hi.
Amy, 你喜欢...魔术吗?
Amy, do you like... magic?
- 我恨你 - 真是抱歉
- I hate you. - I am so sorry.
这是一种病
It's a sickness.
我才是真正的受害者
I'm the real victim here.
2次了, 你2次抢走我的糖果 那本该是属于我的
Twice. Twice in a row, you took my candy. That was my candy.
- 我知道, 不过今晚.. - 不, 想都别想
- I know, but tonight... - no.Forget it.
你这个混蛋
You're such a jackass.
我以为你会叫我傻子
I thought you were gonna call me a jerk.
好吧, 我很抱歉 我会让你成功一次的
All right, I'm sorry.I will make it up to you.
今晚我们去纽约大学附近的酒吧
Tonight, we'll go to a college bar near nyu- the scorpion and the toad.
我想对于年轻人你会显得更加成熟 更加见过世面
I figure in a younger crowd you'll seem more mature, more worldly and,
以及作为一个3年级法律学生 显得更加聪明一点
as a third-year law student, more smarter.
好吧, 不过不许用魔法
Okay, but no magic.
你是怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
我在撒尿, 傻子
I'm taking a leak, dumb ass.
Robin和我在Lily要租的公寓外面见了面
Robin and I met lily outside the next apartment she was seeing.*******
但是我需要自由去追逐我的梦想
But I need the freedom to really chase my passion,
画画或者是音乐 也许是两者皆有
which was painting, but now I think it's music or spoken word- maybe both.
上帝啊, 生活真是美好不是吗?
God!Isn't life amazing?
见到你真是太好了, Ted
It is so great to see you, ted.
我要去锁盒里取钥匙去了
I'm going to get the key from the lockbox.
怎么了?
What?
她太可怜了
She's miserable.
她已经发现自己犯了一个很大的错误
She's realized she's made a huge mistake.
她和Marshall会在一周内复合
Her and marshall will be back together in a week.
我喜欢这样!
I love it!
哦不, 你只是希望Lily变得很可怜
Um, no.You just want lily to be miserable.
但是事实上, 她很开心
The truth is, she's happy.
相信我, 我认识Lily有9年了
Trust me.I've known lily for nine years.
相信我, 我是一个女生
Trust me.I'm a girl.
是的, 不过你是加拿大人
Yeah, but you're canadian.
- 你为什么总是提这个事情? - 你是我们邻居中特殊的一个
- Why do you always have to bring that up? - You're our weird neighbors to the north.
每次你都要提起这个事情
You bring it up every time.
好吧好吧, 5美元打赌她还喜欢Marshall
All right, five bucks says she still wants marshall.
你说吧
You're on.
5美元
Five american bucks.
见鬼
Damn it.
好吧, 那么我们怎么套她的话?
Okay, so how do we get the truth out of her.
龙舌兰酒
Tequila.
这是她的致命伤
It's her weakness.
3杯, 她就无话不说了
Three shots, she'll tell you the truth about anything.
我想这就是我的新家
I hope this is my new home.
好吧, 我想我还是要第一个公寓好了
Yeah, I'm going to take that first apartment.
- Marshall Eriksen, 换衣服 - 不用了
- marshall eriksen, suit up! - No way.
好吧, 你这样还不错
Yeah, you're good in that.
- 走吧 - 等等
- Let's go. - wait.
清空你的口袋
Empty your pockets.
快走
Come on.
- 快点, 我们... - 袖子
- Come on, let'S... - sleeves.
- 没有东西在我的... - 哦, 是吗?
- There is nothing in my... - oh, is that right?
我们走
Let's go.
看看我耳朵后面
behind my ear.
你耳朵后面没有...
There is nothing behind your...
是的, 我在读法律预科
Yeah, I'm in pre-law.
我快死了, 工作量太大了
The workload's killing me, though.
哦, 和我说说
Oh, tell me about it.
我是哥伦比亚大学法学三年级 所以...
I'm third year at columbia law, so...
如果工作量真的会杀了你 那我会定它的罪的
If the workload does kill you, I can probably get a conviction.
好吧
yeah.
你一定是化学专业的 因为我们之间似乎有一种...
You must be majoring in chemistry, 'cause what I'm picking up between us is, uh...
大学女同性恋
college lesbian phase.
听着, 我要走了 不过很希望再次见到你
Listen, I got to go, but it'd be great to see you again.
哦会的
Yes, it would.
真的会的
It really would.
也许还会在这里见到你
Well, maybe I'll see you here sometime.
应该不会了 我从来不来这里, 所以...
Probably not.I'm never here, so...
你知道, 我有电话号码
you know, I do have a phone number.
太棒了
Great.
很好
Nice.
- 嗨, 我叫Barney - 哦, 不
- Hi, I'm barney. - Oh, no.
你介不介意给我的朋友留个电话号码?
Do you... mind giving my friend your phone number?
当然
Sure.
哇哦!
Whoo!
我做到了! 我拿到女生的电话了
I did it!I got a girl's phone number.
哦, 她写的字真可爱, 看
Oh, and her handwriting is so cute, look.
哦, 我想带她出去吃中国菜 然后一起漫步公园
Oh, I'm gonna take her out for chinese food and then maybe we'll walk through the park.
这真是太...怎么了?
It'll be so... what?
抱歉, 伙计 这东西我收下了
Sorry, buddy, I'm taking this one, too.
我想杀了你!
I'll kill you!
然后, 我发现这个地方, 北海滩
And then, I discovered this area, north beach.
最棒的海滩
Best beach ever!
我好像总是在说我的夏天
Oh, I've been blabbering on about my summer.
你们如何?
How are you guys doing?
Marshall怎么样了?
And hey, how's marshall?
- 把卡片给我! - 我不会给你的
- Give me the card! - I'm not giving you any card.
- 我发誓...! - 你不会得到...!
- I swear...! - You are not getting...!
很好
Terrific.
那很好啊
That is so good to hear.
等等
oh, hold on.
应该是关于公寓的事情
This could be about the apartment.
好吧, 我们已经过了审查Lily的时期
okay, we're way past truth-telling-lilly and about to hit
我不想再说什么了
cinco-de-mayo-1998-lilly and I'm not cleaning that up again.
恭喜, 你赢了
So, congratulations, you win.
她的确很开心
She's happy.
我不相信
I didn't get it.
之前那个公寓, 我...
That first apartment,I...
我等的太长了...
I waited too long and...
被别人租走了
somebody else got it.
有趣
interesting.
哇哦, Lily, 你似乎对于这个 有很强的反应
Wow, lily, you, uh... seem to be having a pretty strong reaction on losing an apartment.
我想是不是因为它让你回想起一些失去的东西
I wonder if it's because it reminds you of something else you lost because you couldn't commit.
不, Lily, 你只是为拱型房顶和实木地板才哭的吧
no, lily, you're crying over the crown molding and the real hardwood floors.
没有更深刻的含义了
There's no deeper meaning.
对不对, Lily?
Right, lily?
别哭了, 告诉他
Just quit crying and tell him.
那个公寓代表Marshall
the apartment is a metaphor for marshall.
停! 我打赌你不想看到我生气的样子
stop! You don't want to see what I'm like when I'm angry.
等等!
Hold on!
如果我们没办法好好解决这个问题 那我们谁也别想得到这个号码
If we can't settle this like gentlemen, then no one gets the number.
- 停车! - 什么...?
- stop the cab. - Wha...?
不等等, Marshall!
no, wait.Come on. Marshall!
81街, 谢谢
81st and first, please.
她的字的确很可爱
Ah, she does have cute handwriting.
关于宿醉, 每个人都有自己特殊的疗法
The thing about a hangover is that everyone has their own special remedy.
早上好 想要吃什么?
Waiter: Morning, guys. What can I get you?
给我你们这里最棒的金枪鱼三明治
Bring me the dirtiest, greasiest tuna melt you goT.
还有一瓶牛奶
And a milkshake.
你呢, 先生?
For you, sir?
肉汤
Gravy.
要加点什么吗?
You want that gravy on something?
给我点惊喜吧
Surprise me.
如果我男友不在这里我也想点肉汤
I'd take you with gravy if my boyfriend wasn't sitting right here.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
我什么都不要
I'm good.
你这么活泼干什么?
What are you so chirpy about?
她还醉着呢
She's still drunk from last night.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
听着, 既然你这么想要和Marshall和好 为什么你2天后才问起关于他的事情?
Look, if you want marshall back so bad, how come it took you two days to even ask about him?
我很想问
I was dying to ask.
我只是在装酷
I was just trying to play it cool.
但是真的...
But really...
很好, 我是说工作很不错...
but it's good, I mean, work is great...
拜托, 谈一些关于Marshall的事情
Lily: Come on, say something about marshall.
Marshall在哪里? 他怎么样了? 他现在在做什么?
Where's marshall? How's marshall? What's marshall doing right now?
闭嘴, 谈谈Marshall
Shut up and talk about marshall.
marshall...我要问了!
Marshall, marshall, marshall, marshall... I've got to ask!
Marshall怎么样了?
And hey, how's marshall?
这是一个很糟糕的夏天
It was such an awful summer.
我想回来见他
I just wanted to get back here and see him.
我以为你的夏天很棒
But I thought your summer was great.
并不
Not exactly.
哦上帝啊
Oh, my god.
这就是你的杰作?
This is you best work?
在我的教学生涯中, 从来没见过这么...
In all my years teaching, I've never seen anything so needless.
完全不是艺术的东西...
To say this is... art...
我没法教你
I can't teach you anything.
那些公车上遇到的人呢?
So all those interesting people you met on the bus?
是的, 嗯...
Yeah, um...
我叫Mike
I'm mike.
我是一个反佛教徒冒险旅行作家
I'm a buddhist monk slash adventure travel writer.
我叫Paula
I'm paula.
我是一个专为孩子们唱歌的朋克乐团歌手
I sing in a punk band for children.
我叫Dan, 我是一个神经外科医生
I'm dan. I'm a neurosurgeon.
你真是迷人
You are stunning, by the way.
我一直没和你们联系 因为我没这个脸
I never got in touch because I was too embarrassed.
我的一切都很糟糕
I screwed everything up.
我没用工作, 没有地方住
I have no job, no place to live.
我还失去了我的挚爱
I lost the love of my life.
我知道我没资格这么问
I know I have no right to ask this,
不过你们觉得Marshall还会重新接受我吗?
but do you think marshall would take me back?
这是一次打击
In a heartbeat.
如果你打电话给他 也许他会接受你
If you called him up, yeah, he'd take you back with open arms.
那我应该打电话给他
So maybe I should call him.
也许吧
Maybe.
不! 这个..哇哦!
No!This is... ow!
等等
Hold on.
听着, 如果你打算回去
Look, if you're going to go back to him,
那我就不想听到"也许"这个词
I don't want to hear the word "maybe.
你的字典里没有这个词
" "Maybe" cannot be in your vocabulary.
这次分手差点杀了他
This breakup almost killed him.
他没有办法再承受一次
And he cannot go through it again.
所以, 除非你真的定了心意 不然就离他远点
So, unless you're absolutely certain, stay the hell away from him.
这个人喜欢铜板
This guy likes pennies.
嘿, Marshall
Hi, marshall.
不, 滚开, 我不想和你说话
No, go away.I don't want to talk to you.
好吧, 我知道之前几次我犯了道德上的错误
Okay, I know what I did a couple nights back is in a moral gray area.
但是有一个好消息就是, 她喜欢你
But the great news is, she loved you.
如果事情发生在你身上 你们已经出去好多次了
If things had gone your way - you'd gone out a couple times,
我想她真的会和你做爱
I think she definitely would have had sex with you.
在做爱方面没有"会不会"这个说法
There's no "would" in sex.
你是对的, 我完全... 我完全不擅长这个, Barney
you're right, I totally... I'm just no good at this, barney.
我擅长成双成对 我擅长做Lily的男友
I'm good at being in a couple, I'm good at being lily's boyfriend.
单身, 算了吧
Being single- forget it.
拜托, 你不能放弃
Come on, you can't give up now.
如果我告诉你你可以用同样的对话
What if I told you that you could relive that night with the exact same conversations,
同样的笑话再搞定她一次 而我不来搅局
the exact same jokes only this time, you get her and I don'T.
不可能
That's not possible.
哦, 但是事实如此
Oh, but it is.
她正等着...
She has... wait for it...
来了...快好了...一个一样的双胞胎
Here it comes...Almost there... an identical twin.
好吧!
Yes!
姐妹并不是同一个人
A twin isn't the same person.
当然是
Of course it is.
那你觉得"一样的"是什么意思?
What do you think identical means?
同一个人
"Ident"- same, "ical"- person. Same person.
我们能一起约会
Hey, we could double date.
好吧
Fine.
不过你要发誓, 你不会再抢走这个人
But you have to promise me, you're not going to steal my new twin,
让我和那个老的, 被用过的人独处
and leave me with your old, used-up twin.
被用过的?
Used up?
他们是人类, Marshall
They're a human being, marshall.
然后Marshall叔叔和Barney叔叔 就约了她们姐妹俩一起约会
So uncle marshall and uncle barney went out on a double date with the twins.
你那里如何?
How you doing?
太棒了, 太有趣了
Great. This is so much fun.
我觉得我和那个女孩真的很配
And I think me and the girl are really clicking.
是的, 的确如此
You are, you definitely are.
听着, 你现在必须离开了
Listen, you're going to have to leave now.
我刚和他们俩谈了 我得带他们俩一起回去
I just talked with the twins, and get this, I'm going home with both of them.
是的
Yeah.
这的确发生了
That's happening.
你不能再次对我这么做
It is impossible that you're doing this to me again.
但是她们是双胞胎
But they're twins.
你说过单身就像是在一家糖果店
You... you said to me that being single would be like being in a candy store.
好吧, 并不像在糖果店
Well, it's not, it's not like a candy store.
而是无法无天的的垃圾场
It's a lawless, postapocalyptic wasteland.
- 也许我是你最好的朋友... - Ted才是
- I may be your best friend... - actually ted's my best friend.
但是这个世界上, 男人都是自私的
But in this world, it's every hombre for himself.
这就是单身的真谛所在
That's what being single is.
在9年的囚禁之后...
And after nine years in captivity,
这是我能教你的关于在这个世界上生存的 最关键的一堂课
that is the single greatest lesson I can teach you about surviving in the wild.
现在, 抱歉...
Now, if you'll excuse me...
我有2个特别的复制品在等着我
I have two unique breasts and two duplicates waiting for me.
哦坏消息 Marshall好像吃坏东西了
oh, bad news - marshall got food poisoning.
- 什么? - 哦不
- What? - Oh, no.
太糟糕了, 我挺喜欢他的
That's too bad.I really liked him.
是的
Yeah.
我想今晚我们就三人行吧
Well, I guess we're just a threesome tonight.
Lily, 你在这里做什么?
Lily, what are you doing here?
哦, 我只是路过这里
Oh, oh, I was just walking by.
哦, 你是说纽约?
I wasn'T... oh, you mean new york?
我的任务结束了
My program ended.
很棒
It was just great.
很开心...其实很糟糕
Just lots of fun... it was awful.
这是我犯的最大的错误
It was the worst mistake I ever made.
对不起, Marshall...你好
I'm so sorry, marshall, and... hello.
Lily, 这个夏天是我人生中最糟糕的一次
Lily, this was the worst summer of my life.
我知道, 也是我人生中最糟糕的
I know. It was the worst summer of my life.
这是我这辈子经历的最痛苦的事情
It was the hardest thing that I've ever had to go through.
我们还能重新开始吗?
Can we please get back together?
你之前和我说的那些
All that crap you said to me about,
"我们必须跳出小圈子找到真正的自我"
"we need to figure out who we are outside of us,
"我们要学会单独面对事情"
and we need to learn to do things on our own,"
那些东西都太伤我的心了
it broke my heart.
3个月前, 你伤了我的心
Three months ago, you broke my heart.
我们还能重新开始吗?
Can we please get back together?
Lily, 你之前是对的
Lily, you were right.
那些话也都是正确的
All that crap was right.
所以, 不
So, no.
我们不能再开始了
No, we can't get back together.
我们不应该再开始了
We shouldn'T.
至少, 现在不行
At least, not right now.
好吧
Okay.
是的
Yeah.
我们还能再见面吗?
Well... will we still see each other?
当然
Yeah, yeah.
我想是的
I think so.
我不知道
I don't know.
这些对我来说都是新的
This is all really new to me.
我刚从一段长恋情中走出来
I just got out of a long relationship.
我喜欢你的头发
I like your hair.
谢谢
Thanks.
我那个时候觉得新的城市, 新的颜色...
I figured new city, a different color...
那里还有匹萨 那是我吃过的最差的匹萨
我真高兴回到了纽约
是呀
一切都由你决定...
To even begin to make things up to you...
事实上你能帮我做一点事情
actually there may be something that you can do for me,
但是你不要问我为什么
but you can never ever ask me why.
然后我被提升做了经理助理...
So then I was promoted to assistant mnage-er...
经理...我为什么要这么做?
manager- why do I keep doing that?
Lily?
你害我染上衣原体病, 你个混蛋
You gave me chlamydia, you jerk.
我说到哪里了?
So where was I?
哦是的, 经历助理, 我又做了一次
Ah, yes, assistant mnage-er... I did it again.
我简直无法相信
I can't believe it.
你害我双胞胎妹妹得了衣原体病
You gave my twin sister chlamydia.
你个畜生!
You slime!
等等, 我会魔法
Wha... wait, I know magic.
干的好, Eriksen
Well, played, eriksen.
干的好
Well played.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
时间轴: YTET-13wolf 翻译:Roddick 校对:魔女佳莉 - =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET-13wolf -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
老爸老妈罗曼史 第二季第二集
How I Met Your Mother Season 2 Episode 2